There's always something to fight for.
Black Lotus is a action, crime, mystery film directed by Todor Chapkanov.
An ex-special forces operative wages a one man war through the streets of
Amsterdam to rescue his friend's daughter from the local crime syndicate.
Matteo Donner, played by Rico Verhoeven.
Saban, played by Frank Grillo.
Helene, played by Marie Dompnier.
Angie, played by Pippi Casey.
Shira, played by Rona-Lee Shimon.
Fischer, played by Kevin Janssens.
The White Lotus is an American black comedy drama anthology television series created,
written, and directed by Mike White that premiered on HBO on July 11, 2021.
The series follows the exploits of the guests and staff during a week spent at a
fictional luxury global resort hotel chain called "The White Lotus".
Each season features a different ensemble cast.
Jennifer Coolidge, Natasha Rothwell, and Jon Gries
appear in more than one season.
The first season was filmed and set in Hawaii, the
second in Sicily, and the third in Thailand.
The upcoming fourth season will be filmed and set in France.
The White Lotus was greenlit in October 2020 as a miniseries but was adapted to an anthology series by HBO in August 2021: its second season aired from October
30 to December 11, 2022, and its third season from February 16 to April 6, 2025, after being delayed by the 2023 Writers Guild of America strike.
It is available on HBO Max at the same time as the linear broadcast.
The series has been acclaimed by critics for its writing, acting, characters, humor, and production values and has received several accolades: it has won 16 Primetime
Emmy Awards—including Outstanding Limited or Anthology Series—and two Golden Globes, including Best Limited or Anthology Series or Television Film.
Coolidge won several awards for her performance in the first two
seasons, including two Primetime Emmys and a Golden Globe.
Murray Bartlett also won an Emmy for his performance in the first season, while
White won three Emmys for his writing, directing, and producing.
The film explores themes of amsterdam, netherlands, one man army, crime.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.